Mr. Cheng.
Slow down.
Sister Zhuang asked me to take care of you.
I have to be responsible for you.
If you run so fast,
I won't be able to protect you.
Two cups.
Mr. Cheng.
What are you doing squatting on the floor?
It's too clean.
It is indeed very clean.
Mr. Cheng,
did you find something else?
The victim clearly fell to the ground here.
Then why has such a large area been destroyed?
Mr. Cheng, what's wrong?
Wake up.
Mr. Cheng.
As expected,
there's a problem.
You really have a problem.
I'll call to send you to the hospital now.
No.
I mean,
there's a problem with Mu Weijie's death.
What do you mean?
If you want to know the cause of the victim's death,
the most direct way is to empathize with him.
That is to say,
you had a heart attack just now
because you empathized with the victim?
So what did you find?
Someone came in.
Captain Zhuang,
we found something.
The surface of the body is too clean,
including under the fingernails.
It must have been cleaned by someone.
It seems the victim wasn't alone at the scene.
I don't see anyone here either.
Shh.
He came.
Who was here?
What did he come for?
Mu Weijie died of a heart attack.
But what happened before he fell
that made the scene so messy?
He was hiding.
That person must have wanted to kill him.
Let me go.
Mr. Cheng.
You mean someone hit Mu Weijie last night.
But
there were no wounds on his body.
An accident happened.
On the fallen easel at the scene,
I found strike marks from a wooden stick.
And we extracted crystallized salt stains from the victim's body.
It's sweat.
Right.
It is sweat.
That makes sense.
He sweated a lot before he died.
Plus the smash marks on the easel.
I guess the victim had a conflict with someone before he died.
That person hit the fallen easel with a wooden stick.
To cover up the evidence,
he cleaned all the traces on the body's surface.
You guys haven't left yet.
We made a new discovery during this investigation.
Tell us.
Have some water.
What discovery?
There was another person at the scene.
He attacked Mu Weijie,
and then ran away.
So you guys found out too.
You found out too?
It's not me who found out.
It's us.
We really have to thank Shao for this.
Take a look.
On the evidence at the scene,
I found some slight bump marks.
He also found a lot of sweat stains on the victim,
and that this person had cleaned the victim's body.
Shao,
you're amazing.
Of course.
So,
that person must have broken in with a weapon,
attacked the victim,
before having a chance to cause any harm.
The victim had a heart attack out of fear
and died on the spot.
That's exactly what Mr. Cheng said.
Right?
Right.
Impressive, young man.
I think
the murder weapon
was probably those discarded picture frames scattered at the door.
Agreed.
I noticed that too.
The most easily accessible things in the studio are these picture frames.
And they also match the scratches on the easel.
But I checked all the surveillance near the crime scene last night,
and no one appeared carrying a weapon.
Could it be that the frame was discarded in a surveillance blind spot?
Then we'll have to use the most primitive method
to rule things out.
Mr. Fang.
Take your men to primarily check the trash cans,
green belts, and construction sites.
Focus on the areas with surveillance blind spots.
If we can find this wooden frame strip,
we'll be one step closer to the truth.
Come on.
Qiaoyue, it's me.
I'm back.
Why are you here?
I wanted to see you.
You... you are a murderer now.
You killed someone.
Why are you seeing me instead of hiding?
I didn't kill anyone.
Besides, where can I go?
Did you give a statement to the investigation bureau?
You didn't sell me out, did you?
How could I sell you out?
And if I sold you out,
how could you be here?
Did you go to the studio?
Did you?
I'm telling you.
The police are very smart.
If you've been to the studio,
they will definitely find your fingerprints
and your tracks.
Chances are,
they will find you in a day or two.
If you trust me,
you need to leave right now.
I'll say it again.
I didn't kill anyone.
I didn't even touch him.
I believe you,
but will the police believe it?
Qiaoyue.
Don't touch me.
We have already broken up.
Break up?
Who said we broke up?
I didn't agree to it.
Have you ever been sincere to me all these years?
And now you say
you don't agree?
Qiaoyue.
Qiaoyue, don't forget
who I went to the studio for.
Did I ask you to go?
Qiaoyue, promise me,
you won't tell anyone about this.
If you dare betray me,
I will never let you off.
Xiaoyue,
is that you?
Mind your own business.
It's me, Mom.
Where were you?
Why are you back so late?
Mr. Mu is dead.
Mr. Mu is dead?
How did he die?
You have nothing to do with it, right?
What could it have to do with me?
I was just cooperating with the investigation.
All my studio classmates went.
Don't worry.
Besides, the police said
it was an accidental death.
Hurry, go inside.
I'm coming up.
Stop! Don't run!
This way!
Don't run!
Stop!
Don't move!
Don't run!
Trying to run?
Why are you arresting me?
Shut up!
Take him away.
Go.
Behave.
Trying to run?
Captain Zhuang,
that was brilliant!
Not bad.
Officer,
did you make a mistake?
You're wronging an innocent person.
Let me go.
You've really got the wrong guy.
Stop arguing.
We wouldn't invite you here without evidence.
Besides, if you don't have a guilty conscience,
why did you run?
I didn't run.
I just wanted to catch a ride home quickly.
I'm not a Mancheng local.
Watch your language.
Officer.
Is it a crime to catch a ride home?
Get to the point.
Where were you between 5 p.m. and 7 p.m. on Thursday?
I don't remember.
How could I remember so clearly?
I'm very busy.
Let me help you remember.
You were at Doukou Studio, right?
What happened with Mu Weijie?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Stop wasting your time on me.
You should hurry up and catch the bad guys.
Officer.
What time is it now?
I need to catch my ride home.
Look familiar?
Then can you explain to me
why your fingerprints are on this?